<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Documentation on collaboration-server-protocol</title><link>https://cogru.github.io/collaboration-server-protocol/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Documentation on collaboration-server-protocol</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://cogru.github.io/collaboration-server-protocol/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Overview</title><link>https://cogru.github.io/collaboration-server-protocol/docs/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cogru.github.io/collaboration-server-protocol/docs/overview/</guid><description>This is a placeholder page that shows you how to use this template site.
The Overview is where your users find out about your project. Depending on the size of your docset, you can have a separate overview page (like this one) or put your overview contents in the Documentation landing page (like in the Docsy User Guide).
Try answering these questions for your user in this page:
What is it?</description></item><item><title>Examples</title><link>https://cogru.github.io/collaboration-server-protocol/docs/examples/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cogru.github.io/collaboration-server-protocol/docs/examples/</guid><description>This is a placeholder page that shows you how to use this template site.
Do you have any example applications or code for your users in your repo or elsewhere? Link to your examples here.</description></item><item><title>Concepts</title><link>https://cogru.github.io/collaboration-server-protocol/docs/concepts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cogru.github.io/collaboration-server-protocol/docs/concepts/</guid><description>This is a placeholder page that shows you how to use this template site.
For many projects, users may not need much information beyond the information in the Overview, so this section is optional. However if there are areas where your users will need a more detailed understanding of a given term or feature in order to do anything useful with your project (or to not make mistakes when using it) put that information in this section.</description></item><item><title>Contribution Guidelines</title><link>https://cogru.github.io/collaboration-server-protocol/docs/contribution-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cogru.github.io/collaboration-server-protocol/docs/contribution-guidelines/</guid><description>These basic sample guidelines assume that your Docsy site is deployed using Netlify and your files are stored in GitHub. You can use the guidelines &amp;ldquo;as is&amp;rdquo; or adapt them with your own instructions: for example, other deployment options, information about your doc project&amp;rsquo;s file structure, project-specific review guidelines, versioning guidelines, or any other information your users might find useful when updating your site. Kubeflow has a great example.</description></item></channel></rss>